Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 73-49 Delta Airlines, Incorporated (on behalf of Northeast Airlines, Incorporated) vs. Air Line Pilots Association, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  1/24/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreement, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, TR. Issue: Suspension--Insubordination; Demotion
- 73-50 Osmond Johnson vs. District 65, National Council Distributive Workers of America, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  6/19/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Demotion--Rates of Pay--Reduction.
- 73-51 American Oil Company vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAWIU), Local 8-397, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  9/28/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, TR. Issue: Discharge--Absences--Excessive--Tardiness
- 73-52 City of Syracuse vs. Syracuse Employees American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 400, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  8/7/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, TR. Issue: Rates of Pay--Time Not Worked
- 73-53 Columbia Mills Incorporated vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  9/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 73-54 Georgia-Pacific Corporation vs. United Paper Workers International, Local 140, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  11/5/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Rates of Pay--Holidays--Overtime; Timeliness
- 73-55 C.W. Post College vs. Local 30, International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  7/2/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Management Rights.
- 73-56 General Dynamics Corporation vs. Local 364 Laborer's International Union, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  7/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-57 Mainway Warehouse Incorporated vs. Local 892 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  7/31/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits--Pension, Insurance Plans.
- 73-58 Mobil Chemical Company vs. Local 462 International Brotherhood of Teamster (IBT), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  10/5/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Call-In--Rates of Pay.
- 73-59 Simmons Company vs. Upholsterer's International Union of North America, Local 420, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  6/12/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences--Excessive; Tardiness
- 73-60 New York City Off-Track Betting Corporation vs. District Council #37, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Local 2021, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  6/8/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--Gambling.
- 73-61 Gould, Incorporated vs. Local 418 United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  9/29/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Falsification--Production Records.
- 73-62 Breyer Ice Cream Company vs. Local 757 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  6/19/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Alcoholism--Drinking On The Job.
- 73-63 Island Transportation vs. Local 355 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) Amalgamated Union, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  7/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Negligence and Carelessness.
- 73-64 Pratt Institute vs. Local 1640 American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  7/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 73-65 Celanese Plastics Company vs. Textile Workers Union of America, Local 1166, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  11/21/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Change in Operation--Termination of Employment
- 73-66 Burry Biscuit vs. Local 262 of N.J., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  12/73. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 73-67 American Cyanamid Company vs. Local 111 International Chemical Workers' Union (ICWU), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  11/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-68 Suffolk County vs Suffolk County Patrolmen's Benevolent Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  8/27/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Overtime--Change In Schedule.
- 73-69 N.J. Natural Gas Company vs International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), Locals 1293 and 1820, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  12/11/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discipline--Absences--Reporting.
- 73-70 Elmsford School District #9 vs. Elmsford Teachers Association, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  10/1/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Impasse--Fact-finding
- 73-71 Concord Fabrics, Incorporated vs. District 65 Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union (RWDSU), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  8/16/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination.
- 73-72 Majestic Manufacturing Corporation vs Four Joint Boards of the Pocketbook and Novelty Workers Union, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  9/73. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Postponed
- 73-73 Sealtest Foods vs. Local 584 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  8/7/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Schedules of Work--Change of Schedule.
- 73-74 New York State Narcotic Addiction Control Committee vs. Council 82 American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  1/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Drugs--Sale and Use; Fights and Altercations; Improper Personal Conduct
- 73-75 General American Transportation Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union (OCAW), Local 8-397, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  8/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-76 New York Post Corporation vs. Local 2, New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen Union No. 2, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  2/14/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Schedules of Work--Starting Time Change.
- 73-77 Helene Fuld Hospital vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  9/9/73. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct.
- 73-78 Bell Telephone (Southwestern) vs. Communication Workers of America, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  6/20/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Agreement, Supporting Documents, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Grievance and Grievance Procedures--Procedural Rights.
- 73-79 Long Island Railroad vs. United Transportation Union, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  9/5/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Suspension--Insubordination; Suspension--Reduction.
- 73-80 United Aircraft Corporation vs. Lodge 743 International Association of Machinists (IAM), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- 73-81 Applied Devices Corporation vs. Local 473 International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  11/23/73. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Illness--Sick Pay.
- 73-82 Public Service Gas and Electric vs. Local 274 Gas Appliance Workers, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  10/73. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 73-83 Belair Nursing Home vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  12/31/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Quits--Voluntary--Reinstatement Following.
- 73-84 Continental Can Company vs. United Steelworkers of America (USA), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  9/73. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 73-85 Empire Carpet Company vs. Local 818 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  10/1/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Falsification--Daily Time Record.
- 73-86 Public Health Research Institute vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  9/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Settled.
- 73-87 International Smelting Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 4985, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  12/28/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Transcripts, Supporting Documents. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Fringe Benefits--Pension Plans.
- 73-88 Simmons Company vs. Upholsterers Union Local 420, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  9/26/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 73-89 American Cyanamid vs. Local 111 International Chemical Workers' Union (ICWU), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  10/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-91 Owens-Illinois Company vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  11/73. Settled
- 73-93 State University of New York (SUNY) vs. Senate Professional Association (James K. Thorton), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  2/11/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Grievances--Grievance Procedure--Timeliness; Discrimination--Sex.
- 73-93 State University of New York (SUNY) vs. Senate Professional Association (Norbert Baschnagel and William R. Dando), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  10/73. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled(?).
- 73-94 Lockheed Georgia Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAMAW), Lodge 709, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  1/74. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 73-95 Allied Chemical Corporation vs. Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers' International Union (OCAWIU), Local 8-95, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  2/7/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discharge--Absences--Unauthorized; Alcoholism.
- 73-96 Simmons Company vs. Upholsterer's International Union of America (UIU), Local 1731-Kansas City, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  11/6/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination.
- 73-97 New York State (Rockland State Hospital) Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) (Herbert Byas), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  2/1/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Drugs--Use; Falsification--Time Record; Insubordination.
- 73-98 New York State Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) (Jackson and Riviera), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  11/73. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 73-99 U.S. Pipe and Foundry Company vs. United Steel Workers Local 2026, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  1/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents, TR. Issue: Suspension--Absences--Reporting.
- 73-100 Wilber B. Driver Company vs. United Steelworkers 7225, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  12/73. Settled.
- 73-101 Electronic Products vs. International Chemical Workers, Local 361, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  2/2/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Vacation--Vacation Pay
- 73-102 Owens-Illinois Incorporated vs. Printing Specialties and Paper Products, Local 470, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  12/18/73. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Unsatisfactory Work.
- 73-103 Simmons Company vs. Simmons Elizabeth Employees, Local 420, Upholsterers' International Union, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  11/19/73. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--Negligence and Carelessness; Alcoholism
- 73-104 Fordham Ford, Incorporated vs. Local 259 United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  2/74. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 73-105 Brookhaven National Laboratory vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, Local 2230, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  11/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 73-106 Bordens, Incorporated vs. Joint Board of Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  3/25/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Shift Scheduling--Assignment--Rates of Pay.
- 73-107 Rye Neck Board of Education vs. Rye Neck Teachers' Association, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  4/19/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignments of Jobs--Change of Duties.
- 73-108 Melo Envelope Corporation vs. Printing Specialties Local 447, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  12/73. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 73-109 United Aircraft Corporation vs. International Association of Machinists (IAM), Lodge #743, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  6/13/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreement, TR. Issue: Holiday Pay--Absences
- 73-110 Lazzara Products vs. Local 194 Bakery Drivers, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  1/74. Settled
- 73-111 Syracuse China Corporation vs. International Pottery and Allied Workers, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  3/74. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Rates of Pay--Temporary Job.
- 73-112 E.I. du Pont de Nemous Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union (ICWU), Local 527, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  9/6/74. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Theft.
- 73-113 City of New York (Department of Marine and Aviation) vs. Marine Engineers Beneficial Association (MEBA), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  4/9/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Holiday Pay.
- 73-114 Burns and Roe Construction vs. Local 17 Laborer's International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  12/12/73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Job Attitude--Loafing.
- 73-115 New York City vs. Local 237 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  1/29/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Increase.
- 73-116 Singer Company vs. Local 478 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  3/27/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Unsatisfactory Work.
- 73-117 New York State Correctional Services vs. Ossining Correctional Facility (Brockington), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- 73-118 Exxon Company (Humble Oil) vs. Local 877 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  5/25/74. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Classification--Contract Interpretation
- 73-119 Hudson Pharmaceutical Corporation vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  3/4/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Severance Pay--Management's Obligation To Pay
- 73-120 Country Cousins Shoes, Incorporated vs. Boot and Shoe Workers, Local 773, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  2/4/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Unsatisfactory Work--Insubordination
- 73-121 Carborundum Company vs. Local 8-490, Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  7/3/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Probationary Employees.
- 74-1 New York State Mental Hygiene vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) - Jackson-Rockland Hospital, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  1/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Postponed.
- 74-2 General Dynamics Corporation vs. Marine Draftsmen's Association, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  3/74. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 74-3 Jersey Central Power Light vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), System Council U-3, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  7/9/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Suspension--Insubordination--Refusal of Overtime
- 74-4 Willowbrook State School vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  4/17/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Termination of Employment--Improper Personal Conduct
- 74-5 American Jewish Congress vs. Local 1707, Community and Social Agency Employees Union (CSAEU), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  3/13/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Termination of Employment--Employer's Financial Condition.
- 74-6 Drake Bakeries vs. Bakery Drivers Local 194, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  3/75. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 74-7 U.S. Metals Refining Company vs. United Steelworkers Association (USA), Local 837, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  6/21/74. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Bidding.
- 74-8 Troy Publishing Company vs. Local 23 Albany Printing and Pressmen Union, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  3/20/74. Issue: Overtime--Holiday Pay
- 74-9 Anheuser-Busch, Incorporated vs. Local 153 Joint Board of New Jersey (Box 8, Folder 2)
  RC. Settled
- 74-10 Wolf Auto Sales, Incorporated vs. Local 259 United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  4/22/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Job Attitude.
- 11/74 City of White Plains vs. Patrolmen's Benevolent Association (PBA), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  12/3/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Recall
- 74-11 Westinghouse Electric Company vs. Local 1833 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  7/3/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discharge--Absences, Excessive, Tardiness
- 74-12 Jersey Carpet Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 560, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  4/74. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 74-13 American Cyanamid Company vs. Local 436 International Chemical Workers' Union (ICWU), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- 74-14 W. & J. Sloan Incorporated vs. Local 804 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  4/5/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Improper Job Attitude; Falsification of Records
- 74-15 Mattia Press Incorporated vs. Local 8 Newark Pressmen's Union, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  4/15/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Shift Differential
- 74-16 United Aircraft Corporation vs. Lodge No. 743, International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  7/15/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 74-17 Home News Publishing Company vs. New Jersey Newspaper Guild Local 173, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  8/5/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Promotion--Eligibility.
- 74-18 A & P Bakery vs. Local 262 International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  6/74. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 74-19 General Dynamics (Quincy) vs. Local 5 Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America (IUMSWA), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  7/74. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 74-20 American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) vs. Local 1707 American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  6/24/74. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Job Attitude.
- 74-21 Simmons Company vs. Upholsterer's International Union, Local 420, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  3/19/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations
- 74-22 Bellmore-Merrick School District vs. Bellmore-Merrick Teachers, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  4/74. (No Award), Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Leaves of Absence.
- 74-23 Permacel vs. Transport Workers' Union (TWU), Local 1296, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  3/74. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 74-24 New York State Department of Health and Research Incorporated vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  6/28/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Fringe Benefits--Working Conditions--Parking Privileges
- 74-25 F. W. Woolworth vs Local 804 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  4/10/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Theft
- 74-26 Nestle Company vs. Local 11 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  4/15/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Temporary Agreement--Contract Interpretation
- 74-27 United Air Lines vs. Air Line Pilots Association (ALPA), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  6/74. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 74-28 The Norton Company vs. Lodge 365 International Association of Machinists (IAM), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  6/30/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification
- 74-29 General Dynamics (Electric Boat Division) vs. Local 261 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  6/74. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 74-30 New York City Department of Health vs. District Council 37, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  6/10/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Overtime--Compensation
- 74-31 B.F. Hirsch, Incorporated vs. Local 1 Jewelry, Diamond, and Watch Case Workers' Union, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  6/10/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff--Seniority.
- 74-32 Emery Air Freight Corporation vs. Local 259 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  6/74. (No Award), Routine Correspondence. Issue: Bargaining Units--Supervisors; Performance of Unit Work
- 74-33 Old London Foods, Incorporated vs. Local 138 International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  6/21/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Timeliness--Arbitration; Discharge--Dishonesty--Theft
- 74-34 Allied Aviation Service vs. Local 504 Transport Workers' Union, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  6/1/74. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination
- Kingsbrook Jewish Medical Center vs. Medical Staff Association, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  7/11/74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Fringe Benefits- -Travel Pay
- 74-36 Brookdale Hospital Center vs. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Workers, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  8/13/74. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Promotion--Seniority
- 74-37 Fairchild Republic Company vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  7/74. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 74-38 General Dynamics vs. Local 614 International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  4/74. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 74-40 State of New York (Willowbrook) vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) (Vanessa Simmons), 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)